[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first moons of Jupiter discovered belong to this group.", "correct_answer": "Galilean Moons", "incorrect_answers": ["Ananke group", "Himalia group", "Carme Group"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Barents Sea is named after a Norwegian god.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did director James Cameron get the idea for the 1989 movie The Abyss?", "correct_answer": "From a lecture in high school", "incorrect_answers": ["From a book he read", "From another movie", "From his first sea diving experience"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest island on Earth and one third of it is a national park.", "correct_answer": "Greenland", "incorrect_answers": ["Madagaskar", "Australia", "Alaska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following movie line was said by which actress: Why dont you just say This is the police! and it will open right up!?", "correct_answer": "Stella Stevens to Ernest Borgnine", "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie Murphy to Nick Nolte", "Charles Durning to Burt Reynolds", "Eddie Murphy to Judge Reinhold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of all the symphonies regularly performed, which is the longest?", "correct_answer": "Mahlers Symphony #3 in D minor", "incorrect_answers": ["Stravinskys #14 in B sharp major", "Hayden Symphony #78 in C major", "Beethovens #9 in G minor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The EU has been a western club for most of its history. But which of these western countries has stayed out of the EU?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Spain", "Luxembourg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Windows runs most computers. When the first version of the Windows Operating System released?", "correct_answer": "1981", "incorrect_answers": ["1961", "1991", "1971"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rudolph Abel, considered the greatest Russian spy, was caught in the USA and arrested. What event led to his capture?", "correct_answer": "Somebody picked up a nickel", "incorrect_answers": ["Another spy confessed and gave his name", "He was caught  speeding", "He two-timed his mistress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the prevailing color of the fur of the Tasmanian devil?", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Grey", "White", "Brown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first product to have a bar code?", "correct_answer": "Wrigleys gum", "incorrect_answers": ["Scotts Tissue", "Pez candy", "Bounty bar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tomato Frogs existence is threatened due to what reason?", "correct_answer": "Habitat destruction", "incorrect_answers": ["Their legs are used for food in fine dining restaurants.", "They are hunted for their oils that are used as a skin moisturizer.", "Flooding"]}]